astronutrition.com 2018-10-31

# Privacy Notice - Astronutrition

Effective Date: April 10, 2018

This Privacy Policy applies to the Astro Nutrition (“Site”), a website owned and operated by Longhill Enterprises Ltd. Astro Nutrition (“we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Astro Nutrition when you access the Site and how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our [Terms](https://mouseflow.com/terms/). The use of information collected through our Site shall be limited to the purposes under this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service to customers.

  1. Information We Collect.

(a) Our Service: We may collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, phone number, email address, or similar, when you register for an account. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information. We do not send any promotional emails; however, we may send you service related emails related to your account. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by canceling your account.

(b) Cookies And Tracking Technologies: Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Astro Nutrition and our partners (such as advertising, marketing and analytics), affiliates or analytics or service providers. These technologies may be used in analyzing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by such companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. Our partners may also use such technologies to deliver advertisements to you as described below. We use cookies to remember users’ settings as well as for authentication and analytics. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited.

(c) Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile application each time you access our Site. For example, when you access our Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your operating system, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and other such information. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

(d) Information Related To Data Collected For Our Customers: Astro Nutrition collects information under the direction of its customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose data it may process. If you are a client of one of our current customers and would no longer like to be tracked by such customer, please contact the respective customer directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.

(e) Access And Retention Of Data Controlled By Our Customers: An individual who is a current or former Astro Nutrition customer who seeks access or wishes to correct, amend or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com). An individual who is a client of a current or former Astro Nutrition customer who seeks access or wishes to correct, amend or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the respective customer first and then, if no response is obtained or such response is not satisfactory, should contact to [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com). If we receive a request under this provision, we will acknowledge it within seventy-two (72) business hours and handle it promptly and as required by law.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide our services. Astro Nutrition will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

  1. How We Use Your Information. We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our Site, send you marketing communications, respond to your questions and concerns and to help our partners improve their online offerings.

  1. How We Share Your Information.

(a) Personally Identifiable Information: Astro Nutrition will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Astro Nutrition (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). Any personally identifiable information you elect to make publicly available on our Site, such as posting comments on our blog page, will be available to others. If you remove information that you have made public on our Site, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our Site, or if other users have copied or saved that information. Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for Astro Nutrition and those of our partners.

(c) Instances Where We Are Required To Share Your Information: Astro Nutrition will disclose your information where required to do so by law, if subject to subpoena or other legal proceeding or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Astro Nutrition, our users or others.

(d) What Happens In The Event Of A Change Of Control: We may buy or sell/divest/transfer the company (including any shares in the company), or any combination of its products, services, assets and/or businesses. Your information such as customer names and email addresses, and other User information related to Astro Nutrition may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred in these types of transactions. We may also sell, assign or otherwise transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, reorganizations, liquidations, similar transactions or proceedings involving all or a portion of the company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

(e) Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting: We partner with third parties to display advertising on our Site and manage our advertising on other Sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Site and other Sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools (to learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)). If you access Astro Nutrition on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through the settings.

(f) Testimonials: We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com).

  1. Storage and Processing. Your information collected through Astro Nutrition may be stored and processed in the United States, Europe, or any other country in which Astro Nutrition or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Astro Nutrition may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we will not transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.

  2. How We Protect Your Information. Astro Nutrition is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Astro Nutrition or guarantee that your information on Astro Nutrition may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. When you enter sensitive information (such as log in credentials) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can contact us at [info@astronutrition.com.](mailto:info@astronutrition.com.) We use an outside help platform, and a credit card processing company to bill you if you purchase services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

  3. Privacy Shield. Astro Nutrition self-certifies compliance with [EU-US Privacy Shield](https://mouseflow.com/privacy-shield) at the U.S. Department of Commerce. Astro Nutrition complies with the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC framework as set forth by the European Union regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Astro Nutrition has certified that it adheres to the requirements of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement.

  4. GDPR. Please review our [dedicated page](https://mouseflow.com/gdpr/) to learn more about our approach to GDPR.

  5. Compromise of Personal Information. In the event that personal information is compromised as a breach of security, Astro Nutrition will promptly notify our customers in compliance with applicable law.

  6. Data Access, Correction, Deletion, and Opt Out. For current Astro Nutrition customers, you can review, correct, update or delete inaccuracies to the information about you that Astro Nutrition keeps on file by logging into your account to update your password and billing information. Alternately (for data subjects tracked by Astro Nutrition and for former Astro Nutrition customers), you can contact us directly at [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com). We will acknowledge your request within seventy-two (72) hours and handle it promptly and as required by law. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

  7. Children’s Privacy. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Astro Nutrition does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com).

  8. Notification Procedures. It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by Astro Nutrition in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

  9. Links to Other Web Sites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from Astro Nutrition, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Astro Nutrition to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party website or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.

Social Media Widgets: Our Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and other widgets, that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the organization providing it.

  1. Changes to Our Privacy Policy. All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we change the policy in a material manner, we will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site, prior to the change becoming effective and update the ‘effective date’ at the top of this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [info@astronutrition.com](mailto:info@astronutrition.com), or send mail to:

Longhill Enterprises Ltd.   
210-1085 Howe Street  
Vancouver, BC V6Z1P6  
Canada
